蒙太奇字幕组正在翻译制作中....
此字幕未制作完成 仅供预览和协作之用
我们是一个新成立的靠爱发电字幕组
欢迎一起制作本电影字幕
电报TG加入：MontageSubs
为收集反馈和遇见喜欢这个电影的你
本字幕将采取渐进式发布形式
以下内容可能尚未完全由人工翻译校对 仅供早期预览
欢迎加入蒙太奇字幕组一起制作字幕
无论你是擅长翻译 还是打轴 特效 或者只是想抢先看予以反馈
这里都有你的位置 欢迎加入哦
以下字幕由机器翻译
仅供制作期间前期校准 调轴 预览 参考 人工翻译正在进行中...
可在 github.com/MontageSubs 或者TG群了解进展
哦天哪！嗨！
Oh, my God! Hi!
操 好他妈冷啊！
Fuck, it's fucking cold!
啊啊！
Ahhh!
—你成功了！—我成功了！
-You made it! -I made it!
—我想你！—哦天哪 我想你
-I missed you! -Oh, my God, I missed you,
—我想你！—耶！
-I missed you! -Yay!
救救我 太冷了！
Help me, it's fucking cold!
我真不敢相信你还住在这里
I cannot believe you still live here.
是啊 你每次都这么说
Yeah, well, you say that every time.
我感觉不到我的手了啊！
I can't feel my fucking hands, ah!
—真倒霉 —让我来接手
-Shit me. -Let me take that.
—让我拿着它 —它真的很重
-Let me take that. -It's really heavy.
是的 他妈的 它很重
Yeah, fuck, it is heavy.
你給我帶禮物了嗎？
Did you bring me presents?
哦 不 就像十八双袜子一样
Oh, no, just like eighteen pairs of socks.
我有袜子
I have socks.
是的 但是你的脚很大 宝贝
Yeah, but your feet are huge, babe.
哎哟！好重啊
Ow! It's really heavy.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
—我就是这么想的 —是的
-This is what I think. -Yeah.
当你和一个男人发生性关系时...
When you are having sex with a guy...
是的
Yeah.
—有时...—嗯
-Sometimes... -Mhmm.
他们说的是
They are saying stuff like,
“你喜欢这个 ”
"You like that."
嗯
Mhmm.
你喜欢那个
You like that.
嗯 那到底是什么？
Mhmm. What is that, even?
正确的
Right.
噢 这很深奥
Oh, that's deep.
我认为...我认为他们的意思是
I think... I think they mean
你喜欢...
you like...
-那 -那
-That. -That.
—是啊 “你喜欢我的鸡巴 ”—或者就是这个
-Yeah. "You like my dick." -Or that.
但就像 他们喜欢 就像
But it's like, they like, it's like,
他们的阴茎也是他们的全部
also their dick is their whole self.
所以他们会问 “你喜欢这根鸡巴吗？
So they're like, "Do you like the dick?
你喜欢我吗？”
Do you like me?"
-“你爱我吗？” -“你爱我吗！”
-"Do you love me?" -"Do you love me!"
“而我正在操你......
"And I am fucking you...
-用我的鸡巴 ”-对
-with my dick." -Right.
有时就像...
And sometimes it's like...
不
Don't.
不 有时候就像...
No, sometimes it's like...
哦 天哪
Oh, God.
有时就像...
Sometimes it's like...
有点
Kinda.
—不 是的 —就像……
-No. It is. -It's like...
有时就像你忘记了自己
Sometimes it's like you leave your mind
你从……的角度看它
and you're like, seeing it from, like,
—背后的视角 —在他们的大脑里
-perspective behind. -Inside their brain.
你的屁股看起来很奇怪
Your butt looks weird.
有时就像...对！
Sometimes it's like... right!
那么 你会让我读它吗？
So, are you gonna let me read it?
是的 但还没完
Yeah. But it's not done.
这甚至不是一个正式的草案
It's not even a proper draft.
但这只是一份草稿
But it's a draft.
这绝对是一份草稿
It's definitely a draft.
还是有关纽约同性恋的事情吗？
Is it still about gay New York stuff?
是的 但现在
Yeah, but now it's, like,
黑暗、像心理的 但也很有趣
dark and like psychological, but also funny.
我需要读一下它
I will need to read that.
啊嗬！
Ahoy!
那家伙在跟我们说话吗？
Is that guy talking to us?
呃 我想他只是说了一句“啊嘿”
Ugh, I think he just said, "Ahoy."
喂 邻居！
Ahoy there, neighbor!
啊嗬！
Ahoy!
呃 他占据了我们的位置
Ugh, he's in our spot.
真他妈的地狱
Fuckin' hell.
我希望你还住在这里
I wish you still lived here.
是的
Yeah.
或者至少更接近
Or closer, at least.
是的 我也希望你住得离我近一点
Yeah, I wish you lived closer to me too.
不过我喜欢这里
I like it here, though.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
为什么？
Why?
很多吧？
It's a lot, right?
还在这里
Still being here.
嗯 无论去哪里都有很多事要做
Well, it's a lot to be wherever.
是的 确实如此
Yeah. That's true.
学校就像……
School was like...
呃 研究生院是......呃
Ugh, Grad school was... Ugh.
确切地
Exactly.
即使你结婚了 你还会想念我吗？
Do you miss me even though you're married?
是的 尽管我已结婚 但我仍然想念你
Yes, I miss you even though I'm married.
已婚
Married.
—呃 —真是长大了
-Ugh. -So grown up.
它真的长大了
It's so grown up.
嘿！嘿 你在那边！
Hey! Hey, you over there!
我已结婚！
I'm married!
我加入了一个国家都知道的工会！
I'm in a union that the state knows about!
我爸爸离婚了
My dad is divorced.
—哦 真伤心 —嗯……
-Oh, that's sad. -Um...
没关系
That's okay.
那么我们现在该做什么呢？
Well, what do we do now?
你孤身一人
You're alone.
我不在乎我是否孤独
I don't care whether I'm alone or not.
这是我的权利
It's my right.
这是你的权利
It's your right.
你想干什么？我说他有罪
What do you want? I say he's guilty.
我想听听你的论点
I wanna hear your arguments.
我把我的给了你...
I gave you my...
那个
Ew.
是的...
Yes...
哦
Oh.
—呵呵
-Hi. -Hi.
-我能帮你吗？-呃 不行 抱歉
-Can I help you? -Uh, no. I'm sorry.
我是不是走错房子了？
Do I have the wrong house?
不 这就是正确的房子
No. This is the right house.
-你是... -等一下
-Are you... -Wait.
不不不
No. No.
哦 不 不 不 不 不
Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
是的 这就是房子
This is the house, yeah.
—您在找艾格尼丝吗？—是的 是的
-Are you looking for Agnes? -Yes, yeah.
加文！
Gavin!
—艾格尼丝 —莉迪
-Agnes. -Lydie.
哦 你是莉迪 哦 我的天哪！
Oh, you're Lydie. Oh, my God!
好的 非常抱歉 现在是周末
Okay, I am so sorry, this is the weekend.
是的
Yeah.
—啊 —我错了
-Ah. -My mistake.
没问题 加文是我的邻居
No problem. Gavin is my neighbor.
加文 你实际上住在那里
Gavin, you actually live over there.
哦 是的 我住在那里
Oh, yes. I live there.
—哎呀 —没关系
-Oops. -That's okay.
做个好梦 加文
Sweet dreams, Gavin.
上帝保佑你迷失的灵魂 祝你晚安
God bless your lost soul, and have a good night.
—很高兴见到你 莉迪 —你也是
-It's nice to meet you, Lydie. -You too.
他很可爱
He's cute.
—谁？—你在和他上床
-Who? -You're fucking him.
不 我不是
No, I'm not.
—你在和你的邻居上床 —不 我没有
-You're fucking your neighbor. -No, I'm not.
你正在和你的邻居加文做爱
You're fucking your neighbor named Gavin.
你是
You are.
我不是 我不是
I'm not. I'm not.
—不 我没有 —你在和他上床
-No. I'm not. -You are fucking him.
-我不是 -你他妈的是加文！
-I'm not. -You're fucking Gavin!
—艾格尼丝 —嗯
-Agnes. -Mhmm.
我需要和你谈一些事
I need to talk to you about something.
好的
Okay.
好的 所以这是关于我的身体
Okay. So it's about my body.
哦 你的身材很完美
Oh, your body is perfect.
噢 谢谢
Oh, thank you.
但是 呃 我不是那个意思
But, um, I didn't mean it like that.
好的...
Okay...
所以我体内有一个孩子
So I have a baby in me.
— 你知道吗？— 是的
-You do? -Yeah.
啥？现在就去？
What? Right now?
现在
Right now.
—是的 —什么？！
-Yeah. -What?!
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
哦天哪 你的身体真是个奇迹
Oh, my God. Your body is a miracle.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你害怕吗？
Are you scared?
是啊是啊
Yeah, yeah.
噢 但是你高兴吗？
Oh, but are you glad?
是的 是的 很好
Yeah, yes. It's good.
就像 我显然想要它
Like, I wanted it, obviously.
就像 我们尝试了一百万次
Like, we tried a million times.
是的 你确实想要它
Yeah. You did want it.
—是的 —莉迪……
-Yeah. -Lydie...
你要给它取名叫艾格尼丝吗？
Are you gonna name it Agnes?
哦
Oh.
是啊 我不知道 我不知道
Yeah. I don't know. I don't know.
尝试去想一想
Try and think about it.
哇
Wow.
所以它一定是好精子
So it must have been good sperm.
是的 感谢上帝
Yeah. Thank God for that
随机的 高个白人的好精子
random, tall white guy's good sperm.
也许我也应该为他生孩子
Maybe I should have his babies too
然后他们就可以成为兄弟了
and then they can be brothers.
嗯 他很难被追踪到 所以
Well, he's pretty hard to track down, so.
嗯 我们有他的照片
Well, we have his picture,
这样我们就可以查找他
so we could look him up.
我可以摸一下嗎？
Can I touch it?
是的
Yeah.
我真的没什么感觉
I don't really feel anything.
那是因为它还不像婴儿
That's because it's not like a baby yet.
它有多大了？
How old is it?
十周？
Ten weeks?
所以可能真的很小
So probably really small.
是的
Yeah.
什么？像老鼠一样？
What, like a mouse maybe?
老鼠有多大？
How big is a mouse?
哦 比那还小
Oh, it's smaller than that.
哇 比老鼠还小
Wow, smaller than a mouse.
今晚不要告诉任何人...
Don't tell anyone tonight about...
噢 别担心
Oh, don't worry.
我从不泄露秘密
I never tell secrets
除非我觉得这是一个我真正想说的秘密
unless I feel it is a secret I really wanna tell.
宝贝 这让人很不安
That is not reassuring, babe.
我不想去
I don't wanna go.
不！
No!
不 我们必须这么做 娜塔莎会杀了我的
No, we have to. Natasha will kill me.
我觉得……我觉得她很粗鲁
I feel like... I feel like she's, like, rude,
就像 音调上
like, tonally.
哦 她的语气确实很粗鲁
Oh, she definitely has a very rude tone.
正确的？
Right?
她的语气真的很粗鲁
She's got a really rude tone.
你害怕嗎？
Are you afraid?
—是的 —因为疼痛？
-Yeah. -For the pain?
是的
Yeah.
但也因为它就像一个人
But also because it's like, a person.
我想成为一个真正优秀的人
I wanna make a really good person.
你会成为一个好人的
You're gonna make a good person.
这会很痛
It's gonna hurt so bad.
天啊 好像很疼啊！
Oh, my God, it seems like it hurts so bad!
不！别这么说
No! Don't say that.
我可以这么说
I'm allowed to say that,
你不能这么说
you're not allowed to say that.
啦啦啦 没关系
Blah, blah, blah. Doesn't matter.
简而言之 我们得到了房子
Short story is, we got the house,
但我们必须付钱
but we had to pay, like,
远远超出了我们的预期
significantly more than we wanted to.
你喜欢这房子吗？我的房子？
Do you like this house? My house?
是的 我知道 是的 哦 我的天哪
I, I do. Yeah. Oh, my God.
木头……很漂亮
The wood... it's gorgeous.
味道浓郁 就像黑色的
It's rich. Like dark.
—是的 —你要在里面放什么？
-Yeah. -What are you gonna put in it?
—在我们家？—是的
-In our house? -Yeah.
呃...我们的沙发
Uh... our couch,
我们的床
our bed,
本尼父母的梳妆台
Benny's parents' dresser.
—所有你的东西 —是的 没错
-All your stuff. -Yes. Exactly.
这很有道理
That makes sense.
你现在就像一个成熟的成年人了
You're like a fully fledged adult now.
伙计们 我们有多久没一起出去玩了？
Guys, how long has it been since, like, we've hung out?
我只是有点像...
I'm just sort of like...
你好
Hi.
我们毕业已经三年了？
Is it three years since we graduated?
—我想是四年 —哦 天哪 是四年吗？
-Four, I think. -Oh, my God, is it four years?
是的
Yeah.
时间过得真快
Time really does fly.
但对我和艾格尼丝来说可能不是
But not for me or Agnes probably,
因为我们还在这里 还在学校
since we're still here, still at the school.
你仍旧在你原来的房子里
You're still at your same house.
那栋小房子
That little house.
但对于离开的你们三个人来说 时间可能过得很快
But time probably flies for the three of you who left.
—纽约 —是啊 是啊 纽约
-New York. -Yeah, yeah. New York.
哇
Wow.
对你有好处
Good for you.
嗯 但回来也是一次旅行
Um, but it's a trip being back.
我开车去艾格尼丝学校的路上经过了校园
I drove past the campus on my way to Agnes',
我感觉浑身发冷
and I just got, like, full body chills
当我看到图书馆的时候
when I saw the library.
图书馆 Lydie 不
The library. Lydie, no.
—拜托 —你明白我的意思吗？
-Please. -You know what I mean?
我在那里承受着根深蒂固的压力
I have, like, deeply ingrained stress from that place.
是的 研究生院很疯狂 说实话 我觉得
Yeah, Grad school was wild. I honestly feel like
我研究这篇论文已有十年了
I worked on that thesis for like, a decade.
是啊 就这一次 嗯……
Yeah. This one time, um...
在三楼的一间私人房间里
on the third floor in a private room,
我差点被我的复印件划破脸
I almost paper cut my face open with my copy
去医院
of Little Dorrit just so I could go to the hospital
并睡个好觉
and have a good night's sleep.
我没做过 但是我想过
I didn't do it, but I thought about it.
是的 有时我会做噩梦
Yeah, sometimes I have nightmares
我的论文是这样的
where my thesis is like
全是空白页 然后我把这些页吃掉
all blank pages, and then I eat the pages.
噢 天哪 这太可悲了
Oh, my God, that's so sad.
是啊 真的很难过 呵呵
Yeah. It is really sad, huh.
那么 艾格尼丝 这对你来说真的那么容易吗？
So, Agnes, it was really that easy for you?
没有故事？没什么可分享的？
No story? Nothing to share?
好吧 德克尔最喜欢艾格尼丝 这不是她的错
Well, it's not Agnes' fault that Decker liked her best.
不 这不是她的错
No, it wasn't her fault,
但是 嗯 这让我很生气
but, um, it pissed me off.
一...
Um...
这条鱼太神奇了 它里面……有什么？
This fish is amazing. What's... what's in it?
鱼
Fish.
呃……嗯 你们俩怎么样？
Uh... well, how is it, you two?
你们现在是老师了
You're the teachers now.
我目前还是兼职
I am still part time,
但我想我下学期会教一门课……
but I think I'm gonna teach a class next semester...
他们没说
which they haven't said
是即将发生的事情 但它有可能发生
is what's gonna happen, but it could.
—是的 有可能 —不 它会的
-Yeah, it could. -No. It will.
是的 是的 会的
Yeah. Yes. It, it will.
嗯 我们英语系有消息
Well, we have news in the English department.
艾格尼丝？艾格尼丝有大新闻
Agnes? Agnes has big news.
浴室 抱歉
Bathroom. Sorry.
艾格尼丝现在是一名全职教师
Agnes is now a full-time teacher.
她取代了威尔金森的位置
She took Wilkinson's spot.
填补了空缺
Filled the spot.
艾格尼丝 (Agnes) 担任全职教师还很年轻
Agnes is like super young to be full-time faculty.
是啊 她是五十年来最年轻的 那个婊子
Yeah, she's like the youngest in fifty years, that bitch.
我在开玩笑
I'm kidding.
有一根骨头
There's a bone.
什么？
What?
在魚里
In the fish.
你给我做的鱼好像有骨头似的
There's, like, a bone in the fish that you served me.
对不起
Sorry.
不 这...没关系
No, it's... it's fine.
也许你应该
It's just like maybe you should, like,
在端给人们吃之前 先把它去骨一点
debone it a little bit better before you serve it to people.
你好 我的宝贝
Hello, my baby.
噢 你还是个婴儿
Oh, you're a baby.
我爱你 我爱你
I love you. I love you.
噢 你想下来吗？
Oh, you wanna get down?
好的 我把你放下来
Okay. I'll put you down.
你离开家了 对吗？
You leave the house, right?
是的 我离开家了
Yeah. I leave the house.
我去上班 我有工作 莉迪
I go to work. I have a job, Lydie.
但...
But...
你仍然在同一个办公室
you're still in the same office.
是的
Yes.
艾格尼丝 你说过你要换
Agnes, you said that you were gonna switch.
好吧 我……我不想解释
Well, I... I didn't wanna have to explain
为什么我待在那间办公室里感觉很奇怪
why it's weird for me to be in that office.
也许你应该说有霉菌或别的什么东西
Maybe you should say there's mold or something.
或许
Maybe.
你想让我打电话给他们说
Do you want me to call them and say
墙里有一只死动物？
there's a dead animal in the wall?
你是来自天堂的天使 但不是
You are an angel from heaven, but no.
就像我刚刚得到这份工作一样
It's like, I just got the job.
我甚至不知道我是否应该得到这份工作
I don't even know if I should have the job.
艾格尼丝
Agnes.
我不想抱怨我的办公室
I don't wanna complain about my office,
从技术上来说 这是巨大的
which is technically huge,
光线充足
and there's a lot of light,
我明白他为什么喜欢它
and I can see why he liked it.
不管怎样 是的 我离开了家
Anyways, yes, I leave the house.
艾格尼丝……
Agnes...
不...
don't...
这
die.
我不会死
I'm not gonna die.
如果我要自杀
If I was gonna kill myself,
我会像去年一样这样做……
I would have done it like last year...
或前年
or the year before.
呃 或者 肯定是前一年
Ugh. Or, like, definitely the year before.
艾格尼丝
Agnes.
不 我不会死
No. I'm not gonna die.
让我回报这份感情
Let me return the sentiment.
你千万别死啊
You please don't die.
莉迪亚……
Lydie...
你要生一个小宝宝了
You're having a little baby.
我知道
I know.
你会好好照顾你的小宝宝的
You're gonna take such good care of your little baby.
—我不会死 —请不要死
-I won't die. -Please don't die.
不 你千万别死
No, you please don't die.
你想打个招呼吗？
Do you wanna say hello?
你好
Hi.
我是艾格尼丝
I'm Agnes.
我是你妈妈
I'm your mommy.
Lydie 和 Fran 可能会告诉你其他情况 但请听我说
Lydie and Fran may tell you otherwise, but heed my words.
—我是你的母亲 —艾格尼丝！
-I'm your mother. -Agnes!
—好好做 —嗯 好的
-Do it properly. -Yeah. All right.
你好 我是艾格尼丝
Hi. I'm Agnes.
我不是你的妈妈
I'm not your mommy.
我是你妈妈
I am your mommy.
噢 看在上帝的份上
Oh, for goodness sake.
我感觉到它踢了我一下
I felt it kick.
不 你没有
No, you didn't.
你要...谢谢你
Are you gonna... Thank you.
别去
Don't go.
嘿
Hey.
我很快就会见到你
I'll see you soon.
什么时候？
When?
来纽约吧
Come to New York.
我有一张加床
I've got an extra bed.
告诉弗兰我讨厌他们
Tell Fran that I hate them.
—不 —不 我不讨厌他们
-No. -No, I don't hate them.
我知道 宝贝
I know, babe.
—爱你 —爱你
-Love you. -Love you.
嗯 不
Um, no.
快來吧
Come soon.
不是因为 比如
Not because of, like,
并不是因为我要自杀 而只是……
not because I'm gonna kill myself, but just...
只是...
Just...
不要等那么久才回来
don't wait so long to come back.
好的
Okay.
他妈的！
Fuck!
怎么了？
What is happening?
—发生什么事了？—天啊！
-What's happening? -Oh, my God!
我讨厌学校！
I hate school!
学校真他妈烂！
School fucking sucks!
我的大脑感觉像着火了一样
My brain feels like it's on fire.
就像我快要死了一样！
Like I'm gonna fucking die!
我刚刚意识到 宝贝
I just realized, babe,
没人关心泰德·休斯
no one gives a fuck about Ted Hughes.
不 每个人都关心泰德休斯
No, everyone cares about Ted Hughes.
不不不 我简直不敢相信
No, no, no. I can't believe this.
我花了两年时间写一个人
I spent two years writing about a guy.
我甚至不再睁着眼睛和男人做爱了
I don't even fuck guys with my eyes open anymore.
我只是闭上眼睛想象着女人
I just close my eyes and imagine women.
你想谈论这个吗？
Do you wanna talk about that?
关于什么？
About what?
没有什么
Nothing.
好的 我来了 抱歉 我来了
Okay, I'm here. Sorry, I'm here.
我们做到了吗？
Did we do it?
仅仅
Barely.
—德文？—是的 我做到了
-Devin? -Yes, I did.
真的很抱歉 我其实不拖延
I am so sorry. I don't really procrastinate,
所以这对我来说不算什么
so this wasn't like a whole thing for me.
没关系
That's okay.
继续炫耀吧 它会让你获得成功
Keep showing off, it'll get you places.
莉迪亚
Lydie.
我是莉迪亚
I'm Lydie.
你做完了嗎？
Did you finish?
嗯 是的 嗯...
Uh, yeah, um...
是的 但问题是
Yeah, but the thing is,
别生气 我已经看完了
like, don't be mad. I did finish it.
最后一页就像是复制粘贴的摘录......
The last page is, like, a copy and paste extract of...
《向伯利恒跋涉》不是我写的
"Slouching Towards Bethlehem" that I didn't write.
—耶茨还是迪迪恩？—迪迪恩
-Yates or Didion? -Didion.
永远是迪迪恩
Always Didion.
呃...嘿 你知道吗？
Uh... Hey, you know what?
我应该是你的导师、助手 或者其他什么的
I'm supposed to be your mentor, helper, whatever.
我来这里只是为了确保这件事能够发生
I'm just here to make sure it happens.
我做了我的
I did mine.
好的 很好 那……太好了 娜塔莎
Okay. Good. That's... that's great, Natasha.
Lydie 你认为你能在周三之前完成吗？
Lydie, you think you can finish by Wednesday?
到时候把没有琼的草稿给我吧？
Get me your draft minus the Joan by then?
是啊 又一次……
Yeah, again...
很抱歉
Sorry about that.
你会读我的书吗？
Are you gonna read mine?
当然 这是我的工作
Of course. That's my job.
你要问艾格尼丝她是否做了这件事吗？
Are you gonna ask Agnes if she did hers?
是的
Yeah.
艾格尼丝……
Agnes...
你的情况怎么样？
How'd yours go?
好的 我做到了
Fine. I did it.
迫不及待想读
Can't wait to read.
但你也会读我的 对吧？
But you're gonna read mine too though, right?
是的
Yes.
我为什么还在做这件事？
Why am I still working on this?
因为你还没完成它
Because you didn't finish it.
无意冒犯
No offense.
别吹牛了
Stop bragging.
我不是在吹牛
I'm not bragging.
你的腿靠在墙上
Your legs are on the wall.
所以？
So?
好吧 如果我完成了它
Well, if I'd finished it,
我的腿也会靠在墙上
my legs would be on the wall too,
但我没有
but I haven't.
所以 我的腿不在墙上
So, my legs aren't on the wall.
好的 我会把它们拿下来
Okay. I will take them down.
什么？
What?
你应该操他
You should fuck him.
我不想和他做爱
I don't wanna fuck him.
—真的吗？—是的
-Really? -Yes.
好吧 如果你不想和他上床
Well, if you don't wanna fuck him,
绝对不要和他发生性关系
definitely don't fuck him.
我不会
I won't.
我觉得他想和你做爱
I think he wants to fuck you.
—真的吗？—是的
-Really? -Yeah.
—嗯 真糟糕 —为什么？
-Well, that sucks. -Why?
你认为这就是他说我聪明的原因吗？
Do you think that's why he's telling me I'm smart?
不 我觉得他在告诉你你很聪明
No, I think he's telling you you're smart
因为你真的很聪明
because you're really smart.
好的
Okay.
但你会说什么呢……
What would you say though...
如果他要求你和他做爱？
if he asked you to fuck him?
我会说不
I would say no.
如果他问起的话我会很不高兴
I would be upset if he asked.
我明白
I get that.
我会说不...
I would say no...
但谢谢你
but thank you.
进来吧
Come on in.
你好
Hi.
艾格尼丝 你好
Agnes, hi.
感谢您与我会面
Thanks for meeting with me.
你在忙些什么吗？
Are you working on something?
我是说...
I mean...
不 不 不……
No. Not, not...
并不真地
not really.
好吧 现在你必须告诉我
Well, now you have to tell me.
为什么？
Why?
因为现在我知道的太多了
Because now I know too much.
嗯 好的 嗯……
Uh, yeah, okay. Um...
我正在写一本书
I'm writing a book.
—一本书？—一本书
-A book? -A book.
一本很长的书？
A long book?
-中等 -良好
-Medium. -Good.
为什么？
Why?
嗯 长就像...好的 我们明白了
Well, long is like... okay, we get it.
对 短的就像……
Right. And short is like...
你为什么要写这本书？
Why did you even write a book?
是啊 虽然这是中等的……
Yeah, well, even though this is medium...
—长度刚刚好 —是的
-The perfect length. -Yeah.
我不得不说这太可怕了
I have to say it is horrible,
每次看到它 我就想自杀
and every time I look at it, I wanna kill myself.
毫米
Mm.
嗯 确实有这样的书
Well, there actually have to be books like that
这样我们就可以区分
so that we can distinguish
哪些书才是真正的好书
which books are really the good books.
是的
Yes.
我写这本烂书是为了做公益
I'm doing a public service by writing a shit book.
出色地
Well,
如果有帮助的话
if it helps at all,
我喜欢你的第一部小说
I liked your first novel.
我喜欢它有多糟糕并且......
I liked how fucked up it was and...
这让我觉得这是有原因的
how it made me feel like there's a reason,
即使我看不到 我也知道我还活着
even if I can't see it, that I'm alive.
这并不像小说
And it didn't feel like fiction,
我认为在这种情况下这是一种赞美
which I think is a compliment in this case.
和...
And...
我在做其他事情的时候也一直在想这件事
I think about it all the time when I'm doing other stuff,
就像吃冰淇淋一样
like eating ice cream
或者看着窗外
or looking out the window.
谢谢
Thank you.
好的 呃...
Okay, uh...
一...
Um...
关于我的事就说到这里吧
Enough about me.
我读了你的论文
I read your thesis.
你读得真快
You read it really fast.
是啊 嗯 我 呃...
Yeah, well, I, uh...
说实话 我实在无法放下它
to be honest, I couldn't put it down.
有人把你的手粘在上面吗？
Someone glue your hands to it?
什么？
What?
—哦...—对不起
-Oh... -I'm sorry.
基本上没有任何意义
Makes basically no sense.
不 确实如此
No, it does.
一...
Um...
是的
Yeah.
— 无论如何 所以 呃... — 是啊
-Anyway, so, uh... -Yeah.
整个部分
This whole section
从第三页到第七页
from page three through seven,
我发现这绝对公正……
I find to be absolutely just...
非凡的
extraordinary.
真的
Really.
对不起
Sorry.
抱歉 我的前任是一名检察官 这......
Sorry, my ex is a prosecutor, which...
哦 哇 法律
Oh, wow, the law.
是的 我的前妻……
Yeah. My ex-wife...
热爱法律
loves the law.
她在法庭上 我的孩子病了 我必须……
She's in court, my kid's sick. I have to...
我得跑了
I've gotta run.
—操 对不起 —哦 没关系
-Fuck, sorry. -Oh, that's okay.
你应该引起我的全部注意
You should have my full attention,
坦白说 这篇论文值得得到这样的评价
and frankly, this paper deserves that.
—我们可以稍后再安排 —好的 没问题
-We can reschedule for later. -Yeah, that's fine.
好的 我得...我会给你发短信
All right, I gotta... I'll text you.
—好的 —我会 呃……
-Okay. -I'll, uh...
抱歉 我不得不这样跑
Sorry I have to run like this.
—哦 没关系 —哦 实际上
-Oh, that's okay. -Oh, actually,
你应该看看这个
you should look at this.
我刚刚收到
I just got it.
《到灯塔去》第一版
First edition To The Lighthouse.
哇 哇 谢谢
Wow, wow. Thank you.
是的
Yeah.
我可以摸一下嗎？
Can I touch it?
—是的 —好的
-Yeah. -Okay.
好的
All right.
我们被要求考虑这个想法
We are asked to reckon with the idea
夺走他的生命
that taking his life,
逃离物质存在
taking flight from the corporeal existence,
也许是给 Milkman 的
is perhaps for Milkman
这是一场超越 而非悲剧
a transcendence and not a tragedy.
米尔克曼感觉自己正在回到祖籍地
Milkman feels he is returning to his ancestral home.
—艾格尼丝 —嗨
-Agnes. -Hi.
太好了 好的 呃……
Great. Okay. Uh...
感谢您最后一刻的到来
Thanks for coming last minute.
抱歉 这是我家
Sorry, it's my house.
—希望没问题 —是的 是的 没问题
-Hope that's okay. -Yeah, yeah, no problem.
别担心 我的……
Don't worry, my...
我的孩子和我前任在一起
my kid's with my ex.
一切都很好
It's all good.
—呃 进来吧 —好的
-Uh, come on in. -Okay.
哦 你介意脱掉靴子吗？
Oh, do you mind taking your boots off?
哦 是的
Oh, yeah.
—呃 —不
-Duh. -No.
—抱歉 —别抱歉
-Sorry. -Don't be sorry.
你有我的论文吗？
Do you have my thesis?
哦 是的 是的 是的 是的
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
你的鞋带松了
Your shoes are untied.
哦
Ooh.
嘿 我真是一直在屏息等待
Hey, I've been literally waiting with bated breath.
进展如何？
How did it go?
艾格尼丝 你还好吗？
Agnes, are you okay?
发生了什么？
What happened?
我不知道
I don't know.
我的裤子破了
My pants are broken.
然后我们开始接吻
And then we started kissing.
我以为我们在接吻
And I thought, we're kissing.
我以为我们一直在接吻
I was thinking we were kissing the whole time,
就像以一种不好的方式
like in a bad way
当你过得不开心的时候
where you aren't having a good time,
就像某人的嘴一样
and it's just like someone's mouth.
然后我说
And then I said,
“我真的不认为我准备好接吻了
"I don't really think I'm ready to be kissing.
我刚刚摆脱了一件事 ”
I just got out of a thing."
这是我编造的
Which is something I made up.
对此撒谎是可以的
It's okay to lie about that.
然后他说 “没关系 ”
And then he said, "That's okay."
“我们可以坐在沙发上看电影 ”
"We can just sit on the couch and watch a movie."
于是他开始玩一些东西
So he started playing something.
它是动画的 我认为这很奇怪
It was animated, which I thought was weird.
但后来我想起他有个孩子
But then I remembered he has a kid,
这样就没那么奇怪了
so that made it less weird.
然后他开始把手放在我的裤子上
Then he started putting his hand on my pants,
我正把它移开
and I was kinda moving it away.
但他一直把它移回我的裤子里
But he kept moving it back to my pants,
然后他开始把手伸进我的裤子里 就像
and then he started putting his hand down my pants, like,
在裤子和内衣之间
in between the pants and my underwear.
我的身体扭动得像……
And I was kinda squirming my body like...
他是……
he was...
他的手指非常有力且坚硬
his fingers were really strong and hard,
就像 以不好的方式
like, in the bad way.
就像 这太难了
Like, it was too hard.
也许感觉会很好
Maybe it would've felt good
如果我希望他的手指能做到这一点
if I wanted his fingers to be doing that.
但你并不想要那样
But you didn't want that.
不 我没有
No, I didn't.
然后 我把他的手拉了出来 因为……
And then, I pulled his hand out because...
感觉不太好
it didn't feel good,
而且确实有点疼
and it actually hurt, kinda.
然后我开始亲吻他
And then I started kissing him
因为我认为
because I thought,
“好吧 如果我们必须做点什么的话 ”
"Well, if we have to be doing something,"
“我宁愿亲吻 也不愿他的手指伸进去 ”
"I'd rather it be kissing than his fingers down there."
然后我就不记得了
And then I don't remember.
然后在某个时刻
And then at some point,
他的手又伸进了我的内裤
his hand was back in my underwear.
但现在在内衣下面
But under the underwear now.
我又试图把它移开
And I was trying to move it away again.
听起来你曾多次试图将它移开
Sounds like you were trying to move it away a lot.
是的 我一直这么想
Yeah. That's what I kept thinking.
就像 再来一次 他就不会再把它移回去
Like, one more time and he won't move it back
因为它太明显了 所以我把它移开了
because it's so obvious I'm moving it away.
但他一直将其移回
But he kept moving it back.
进而...
And then...
他正在拉下我的裤子……
he was pulling down my pants...
嗯 他试图把它们拉下来
Well, he was trying to pull them down,
但它们有一个按钮
but they have a button.
所以他一直拉啊拉
So he was pulling, pulling.
我把它们拉了回来
And I was pulling them back up.
然后他们就走到了半山腰
And then they were halfway down.
我感觉有什么东西进入了我的体内
And I felt something go in, like, in me,
我的脊椎开始发凉
and my spine got cold.
我伸手去摸它 然后……
And I reached down to feel it and...
这是……
It was...
就是他……你知道吗？
It was him... you know?
然后我跳了起来......
And then I jumped up and...
我坐在沙发边上
I sat on the side of the couch.
我不知道要多久
I don't know how long.
我看了一眼他的脸
And I looked at his face once,
它看起来好像很害怕
and it was, like, scared.
—他的脸上露出了害怕的表情？—是的
-His face was scared? -Yes.
然后我就慢慢地站了起来
And then I just got up kinda slowly,
我抓起靴子
and I grabbed my boots,
然后我开车回家
and I drove home,
现在我在这里
and now I'm here.
听起来像...
That sounds like...
那
that.
那是...
That is...
就是这样
that's the thing.
我真的非常非常抱歉
I'm really, really sorry.
我不知道我是否应该完全赤裸
I never know if I'm supposed to get fully naked.
—就像穿着长袍一样？—是的
-Like in the gown? -Yeah.
—你现在裸体吗？—是的
-Are you naked right now? -Yes.
兄弟 我认为你不应该裸体
Dude, I don't think you're supposed to be naked.
你好 你是艾格尼丝吗？
Hi. You're Agnes?
—是的 你好 —我是埃文斯医生
-Yeah, hi. -I'm doctor Evans.
你被性侵了吗？
You were sexually assaulted?
嗯 是的
Uh, yeah.
你现在觉得安全吗？
Do you feel safe now?
抱歉 在我们这样做之前
Sorry, before... uh, we do that,
我只是想让你知道我全身赤裸
I just want you to know that I'm fully naked.
-什么？-在长袍下面 可以吗？
-What? -Under the robe. Is that okay?
嗯 没问题
Yeah. That's fine.
—你介意吗？—当然可以
-Do you mind? -Yeah, sure.
那么 这是什么时候发生的？
So, when did this happen?
那件事？
The thing?
—袭击 —昨晚
-The assault. -Last night.
昨天晚上
Last evening.
Yesterday evening.
—你洗澡了吗？—我洗了个澡
-And have you showered? -I took a bath.
所以最好去急诊室
So it's usually best to go to the emergency room
就在这样的事情发生之后
right after something like this happens.
哦好的
Oh, okay.
下次我一定会记住这一点
I will definitely keep that in mind for the next time.
嗯 这时候我们会用
Well, that's when we would use
性侵犯法医证据工具包
a sexual assault forensic evidence kit.
哦 好的 我觉得你只需要……
Oh, okay. I feel like you just need to...
音调上偏离了音调
tonally shift away from the tone
你现在正在服用
you're taking right now.
就像 我们只是需要音调的转变
Like, we just need a tonal shift.
只是想确认他没有给我任何东西
Just wanna make sure he didn't give me anything,
比如 阴道或者
like, vaginally or yeah.
袭击者在你体内射精了吗？
Did your attacker ejaculate in you?
嗯 我不会称他为袭击我的人
Um, well, I wouldn't call him my attacker.
这不像是 呸！
It wasn't like, bah!
但你被强奸了
But you were raped.
—哇哦 —是的
-Whoa. -Yeah.
说得好
And well put.
我知道这很难说
I know this is hard to talk about.
感觉你不知道这一点
It doesn't feel that you know that.
这些问题是礼仪问题
These questions are protocol.
是的 你问他们的方式真的很怪异
Yeah, you're asking them in a really freaky way.
冷静一下 女士
Calm down, ma'am.
—哦 她很冷静 —我很冷静
-Oh, she's calm. -I'm calm.
你可以继续提问了
You can finish your questions.
他射精到你体内了吗？
Did he ejaculate in you?
可怕的词
Horrible word.
不 他实际上在我体内
No, the actual him being inside me part
没过多久 就像……
wasn't that long, it was like...
—那么久 —好的
-that long. -Okay.
所以 我们会进行血液检查 检查你是否怀孕
So, we'll do a blood test to check you for pregnancy
以及性传播感染
and sexually transmitted infections,
然后我们会进行宫颈培养
and then we'll do a cervix culture.
-嗯 -什么事？
-Yum. -Excuse me?
她说好吃
She said yum.
我马上回来 我们就可以开始了
I'll be right back, and we can get started.
—艾格尼丝？—嗯
-Agnes? -Mhmm.
他要走了
He's leaving.
WHO？
Who?
德克尔正在转学
Decker's transferring.
他在纽约北部找到了一份工作
He got a job in New York. Upstate.
他要走了
He's leaving.
他妈的
Fuck.
搞什么鬼？
What the fuck?
这样好吗？
Is this good?
不
No.
也许吧 我不知道
Maybe. I don't know.
他对此有何评论？
Did he say anything about this?
不
No.
昨天他的办公桌非常乱
And yesterday his desk was, like, really cluttered.
就像他没有打包任何东西一样
Like he wasn't packed or anything.
所以他正在跑步
So he's running.
他妈的
Fuck.
—嗨 我是...—艾格尼丝
-Hi, I'm... -Agnes.
嗨 我是伊丽莎白 这是克莱尔
Hi, I'm Elizabeth. This is Claire.
-嗨 艾格尼丝 我是克莱尔 -嗨
-Hi, Agnes. I'm Claire. -Hi.
你介意跟我们一起回去吗？
Do you mind coming back with us?
当然
Sure.
得知您遭遇此事 我们深感抱歉
We are so sorry to hear this happened to you.
我们正在采取这一行动
We are taking this
真的很认真
really seriously.
你会做什么吗？
Are you gonna do anything?
我们将开始调查
We would begin an investigation.
但正如你可能听说的那样
But as you may have heard,
他昨天在……递交了辞职信
he sent in his letter of resignation yesterday at...
下午 4:18
4:18 p.m.
您于今天上午 8:42 报告了此事
And you reported this today at 8:42 am.
好的
Okay.
不幸的是 他不再受雇于我们了
Unfortunately, he's no longer under our employ.
因此我们不能采取通常采取的措施
So we can't take the measures that we would normally take
比如暂停他或者解雇他或者……
such as suspending him or letting him go or...
类似这样的事情
things of that nature.
这些事情真的很难
These things are really hard,
不幸的是 大学无法
and the University is unfortunately unable
承担任何责任
to take any kind of responsibility.
但他是我的顾问
But he was my advisor.
前任顾问
Former advisor.
您可以选择
You have the option
去警察局报案
of going to the police station and reporting this
并发出逮捕令
and issuing an arrest warrant.
我们知道你正在经历什么
We know what you're going through.
我们是女人
We are women.
什么？
What?
我们是女人
We are women.
你好
Hi.
你是我的邻居 对吗？
You're my neighbor, right?
是的 我住在这里
Yeah, I live here.
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
哦 呃 加文
Oh, uh, Gavin.
加文 很高兴见到你
Gavin, nice to meet you.
—你也是 —我是艾格尼丝
-You too. -I'm Agnes.
上帝的羔羊
Lamb of God.
—什么？—没什么
-What? -That's nothing.
一切都很好 我只是 呃……
It's all good, I'm just, uh...
一...
Um...
这么美好的夜晚你有什么打算？
What are you up to this fine evening?
哦 我想知道 你有没有
Oh, I was wondering, do you have,
比如 能引起火灾的东西？
like, stuff that makes a fire?
哦 嗯……
Oh, um...
—火柴？—不 像液体
-Matches? -No, like a liquid.
—有这样的事吗？—哦 是的
-Is that a thing? -Oh, yes.
-打火机油 -是的 你有吗？
-Lighter fluid. -Yes. Do you have that?
是的
Yes.
你为什么需要它？
Why do you need it?
嗯 我和我的朋友们
Um, my friends and I,
我们要做热狗
we're gonna make, like, hot dogs.
哦 热狗听起来不错
Oh, hot dog sounds good.
哦 对不起 我们只买了两条热狗
Oh, I'm sorry, we only bought two hot dogs.
哦 不 没问题 我……
Oh, no, that's no problem, I'm...
我和妈妈有晚餐计划
I have dinner plans with my mom.
事实并非如此
That's not true.
对不起 我只是想把自己封闭起来
I'm sorry, I just wanted to close myself off
避免被拒绝的可能性
from the possibility of being rejected.
没问题
That's no problem.
—我去拿打火机油 —好的
-I'll get the lighter fluid. -Okay.
我看的时候你想进来吗？
Do you wanna come inside while I look?
呃 不行 抱歉 我可以外面等吗？
Uh, no, sorry. Can I wait outside?
是的 别担心
Yeah. Don't worry about it.
嗯 我很快就回来
Um, I'll be back soon.
这应该可以解决问题
This should do the trick.
太好了 谢谢
Great, thanks.
那么我是不是只需要把这个倒在
And so do I just pour this on the thing
我想着火吗？
I want to be on fire?
在烧烤上？
On the barbecue?
—是的 —嗯 是的
-Yes. -Uh, yeah,
不要放太多
don't put too much of it on there.
好的
Okay.
你...需要我的帮助吗？
Do you... do you want my help?
不
No.
谢谢...
Thank you...
—加文 —加文
-Gavin. -Gavin.
是的 非常感谢 Gavin
Yes. Thank you, definitely, Gavin.
呃 你不住那边吗？
Uh, don't you live over there?
哈！是啊 我……是啊 绝对的 哎呀
Ha! Yup, I... yup, definitely. Oops.
你为什么会有这个？
Why do you have that?
我从邻居那里得到它
I got it from the neighbor.
为什么？
Why?
这绝对不是
It's definitely not, like,
良好或正常的思路
a good or normal train of thought.
好的
Okay.
我想我要放火烧德克尔的办公室
I think I was gonna light Decker's office on fire.
好的...
Okay...
你还想做吗？
Do you still wanna do it?
我不知道
I don't know.
我会做
I will do it.
那真是太好了
That's really nice.
—但是不是 —不 说真的
-But no. -No, seriously.
如果你需要有人烧毁他的办公室
If you need someone to burn his office down,
但你不想自己做
but you don't wanna do it yourself,
我会做
I will do it.
不 我甚至不想让他死
No, I don't even want him to die.
我愿意
I do.
我不想让他死
I don't want him to die.
好吧 如果你改变主意的话……
Well, if you change your mind...
谢谢
Thanks.
也许我们可以烧一些小一点的东西
Maybe we could burn something smaller,
比如他的头发或者他的笔或者别的什么
like his hair or his pens or something.
我会考虑的
I'll think about that.
好的
Okay.
我要做热狗
I have to make hot dogs.
哦 为什么？
Oh, why?
我告诉邻居 这简直就是一个弥天大谎
I told the neighbor, it's like this whole big lie.
我陷入了谎言之中
I'm stuck in a lie.
好的 我会做的
Okay. I will do it.
—对不起 —不 没关系
-I'm sorry. -No, it's fine.
我本来要去杀一个人 所以这容易多了
I was gonna, like, kill a man, so this is much easier.
我们有热狗吗？
Do we have hot dogs?
我不知道
I don't know.
你好
Hi.
好的 我去喝咖啡
Okay. I'm going to get coffee.
你要我去接你吗？
Do you want me to pick you up?
好吧 操
Well, fuck.
这真是太好了
This is really nice.
我猜嗯...
I guess um...
是的 我爱你
Yup. I love you.
你想来喝咖啡吗？
You wanna come get coffee?
三文鱼
Salmon.
好吧 你很挑剔 这是一种优秀的品质
All right, you're picky, an excellent quality.
金枪鱼
Tuna.
也许你只是闻到了罐头的味道
Maybe you're just smelling the can.
里面有金枪鱼
There's tuna inside.
好的 每种一个
All right, one of each.
嘿
Hey.
这就是你今天要讲的全部内容吗？
Is this all for you today?
是的 谢谢
Yes, thank you.
你带猫进杂货店了吗？
Did you bring a cat into the grocery store?
不
No.
是的 你做到了
Yes, you did.
你说什么？
What did you say?
你在撒谎
You're lying.
不 我不是
No, I'm not.
这是你的猫粮
Here's your cat food.
我们的咖啡喝完了
We ran out of coffee.
我有一些
I got some.
我养了一只猫
I got a cat.
无论你需要什么
Whatever you need.
感谢您来到这里并完成您的传唤
Thank you for being here and completing your summons.
对于那些还没有这样做的人
For those of you who haven't done this
不知道会发生什么
and don't know what to expect,
请上来
please come up
并得到一份调查问卷
and get a questionnaire.
填写
Fill it out
并将其完整地返回给我们
and return it to us completed.
我们有小铅笔
We have little pencils
如果你需要一支小铅笔
if you need a little pencil.
以下陪审员被解散
The following jurors are dismissed.
陪审员一、三、五
Juror one, three, five,
七、八、
seven, eight,
30 32
30, 32,
39 25
39, 25,
42、43、
42, 43,
49 59
49, 59.
你被解雇了
You are dismissed.
谢谢
Thank you.
你可以走了
You can go.
富勒夫人 您觉得呢？
And do you think, Mrs. Fuller,
根据该定义
based on that definition,
你明白“排除合理怀疑”的意思吗？
you understand the meaning of beyond a reasonable doubt?
是的
Yes.
毫无疑问地确信
That to be convinced beyond a shadow of a doubt,
你一定去过那里
you must have been there
并亲眼目睹了犯罪行为？
and seen the crime with your own eyes?
是的 我明白
Yes. I understand.
你们其他人是否觉得
And do the rest of you feel
你可以应用这个想法 毫无疑问
you can apply that idea, beyond a reasonable doubt,
—对于这个案子？—嗯
-to this case? -Mhmm.
你们当中有多少人有孩子？
How many of you have children?
呃 沃加德先生
Uh, Mr. Woguard.
你有孩子吗？
You have a child?
嗯 是的 索菲刚满四岁
Uh, yes. Soph just turned four.
假设你和你的女儿在公园
Say you and your daughter were at the park
她正在玩攀爬架
and she's playing on the monkey bars.
你转过身去几分钟
And you turned your back for a few minutes,
然后她就带着断掉的手臂跑向你
and then she runs over to you with a broken arm.
您认为会发生什么？
What would you think happened?
她从攀爬架上摔了下来
She fell off the monkey bars
并打断了她的手臂
and broke her arm.
是的 这是一个例子
Yes, so that's an example
间接证据
of circumstantial evidence.
这就是你可以合理推断的
That's what you can reasonably infer
根据你所掌握的事实
based on the facts that you have.
这有道理吗 沃加德先生？
Does this make sense, Mr. Woguard?
是的
Yes.
如果另一个孩子跑向你
And if instead another child ran over to you
并告诉你他看到她从攀爬架上摔下来
and told you he saw her fall off the monkey bars,
这是直接的证词
that's direct testimony
因为有人目睹了这一切
because someone witnessed it.
大家明白这个区别吗？
Does everybody understand that difference,
间接证据之间
between circumstantial evidence
和直接证词？
and direct testimony?
嗯
Mhmm.
在没有直接证词的情况下
Without direct testimony,
我们不能肯定
we cannot be positively certain
犯罪已经发生
a crime has been committed.
正如检方所说
As the prosecution,
我必须证明被告有罪
I must prove the defendant's guilt
毫无合理怀疑
beyond a reasonable doubt.
意思是 没有其他合理的解释
Meaning, that there is no other reasonable explanation
这可以从所提供的证据中得出
that can come from evidence presented.
如果你们当中有人成为犯罪的受害者
If any of you have been victims of a crime,
请举手
please raise your hand.
呃 费伯先生 犯罪内容是什么？
Uh, Mr. Faber, what was the crime?
呃 我被抢劫了 被枪指着
Uh, I was robbed. At gunpoint.
你有什么理由相信
Do you have any reason to believe
这段经历会让你无法服务
that experience would make you unable to serve
作为本次审判的公正陪审员？
as an impartial juror on this trial?
不
No.
沃德小姐
Miss Ward.
什么？
What?
当我问谁是犯罪的受害者时
When I asked who has been a victim of a crime,
你举手了吗？
did you raise your hand?
不 我意识到我不应该分享它
No, I realized I shouldn't share it.
所以...
So...
你不能分担罪行吗？
You're unable to share the crime?
一...
Um...
坦白说这是我最可怕的噩梦
It is frankly my worst nightmare
必须告诉整个房间的陌生人
to have to tell this whole room of strangers
关于发生在我身上的事
about the thing that happened to me.
所以...
So...
这就是我没有决定的原因
that is the reasoning as to why I did not decide
继续举手
to continue having my hand raised.
谢谢
Thank you.
你认为该罪行会导致你无法服役
Do you think the crime would make you unable to serve
作为此案的公正陪审员？
as an impartial juror on this case?
这是个好问题
That is a good question,
这也是我一直在思考的问题
and one I've been thinking about.
你得出什么结论了吗？
Have you come to any conclusions?
你知道 我想我会更好
You know, I think I would be better
不在陪审团中
not being on the jury
反而会做得更好
and instead would do better
履行不同的公民角色
fulfilling a different civic role.
您心目中的公民角色是什么样的？
And what kind of civic role do you have in mind?
所以 谢谢你的提问
So, thank you for asking.
我其实是一名教授
I am actually a professor,
兼职 希望很快能成为全职
part-time, hopefully soon full-time,
其中 教学是重要的工作
which, teaching is important work.
我认为教学很重要
I think teaching is important.
有人会说老师是理想的陪审员
Some would say that a teacher makes an ideal juror.
绝对不是 不是
Absolutely not, no.
在您的问卷上 您写道……
On your questionnaire, you wrote...
哦 不 不
Oh, no, no.
我不知道我们会大声朗读这些 所以
I did not know that we would be reading those aloud, so.
“你的朋友会如何形容你？”
"How would your friends describe you?"
“聪明的 ”
"Smart."
划掉“tall”这个词
Crossed out, then the word "tall."
如果你所遭受的犯罪行为使你产生偏见
If the crime you were a victim of makes you biased,
我们将解雇你
we will dismiss you.
我告诉你这件事会惹上麻烦吗？
Can I get in trouble for telling you?
如果你是受害者 为什么你会遇到麻烦？
Why would you get in trouble if you were the victim?
我不知道
I don't know.
我认为这项法律毫无意义
The law makes no sense in my opinion.
我...
I...
事实上我之前没有大声说过
I haven't said it out loud actually before.
嗯 没关系
Well, that's okay.
你去报警了吗？
Did you go to the police?
不
No.
我只有一个按钮
All I had was a button,
我不想让他进监狱
and I don't want him to go to jail.
这是为什么？
Why is that?
他有一个孩子
He has a kid.
我希望他不要再做这样的事
I want him to stop being someone who does that.
如果他进了监狱
And if he went to jail,
他只是做了这样的事 现在却被关在监狱里
he'd just be someone who does that, who's now in jail.
法官大人 我可以上法官席吗？
Your honor, may I approach the bench?
艾格尼丝·沃德 你被原谅了
Agnes Ward, you are excused.
对不起
I'm sorry.
书记员 您可以传唤下一位陪审员了
Clerk, you may call the next juror.
好的 我们现在就打电话……
Okay. We'll now call up...
雷克斯·哈伯曼
Rex Haberman.
雷克斯？
Rex?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你玩得开心嗎？
Did you have a good time?
什么？
What?
你喜欢我们刚才的性爱吗？
Did you like the sex we just had?
嗯
Mhmm.
好的
Okay.
Good.
谢谢
Thank you.
艾格尼丝 我们收到了非常积极的反馈
Agnes, we've gotten incredibly positive feedback
来自讨论部分的学生
from the students in your discussion section
关于你的兼职贡献
about your part-time contribution
到这所大学
to this university.
来自现任教职人员、前任教职人员、
From current faculty, former faculty,
一切都闪闪发光
it's just all glowing.
—以前是教员吗？—是的
-Former faculty? -Yes.
你被叫来了 让我看看
You've been called, let's see,
有帮助的
helpful,
支持
supportive,
非凡的
extraordinary.
我们知道有人在谈论这里的空位
We know there's been talk about the open spot here
自从普雷斯顿离开后 我们就没有……
since Preston left, we haven't...
好吧 我们想找到适合该计划的方案
well, we wanted to find the right fit for the program.
我们很高兴终于能为您提供
And we are thrilled to finally offer you
费尔波特的全职教学职位
a full-time teaching position here at Fairport.
真的吗？
Really?
是的 是的
Yes, yes.
该部门一致投票
The department voted unanimously.
哇 我接受
Wow. I accept.
了不起
Terrific.
你将教授我们的入门课程
You'll teach our introductory course,
《二十世纪小说》
"The Twentieth Century Novel,"
你曾领导过几次
which you've led a few times,
您还可以创建自己的选修课
and you'll also create your own elective.
我们希望您考虑
We would love for you to consider
教授短篇小说艺术课
teaching a class on the art of the short story
因为我们都读过你的论文
since we all read your thesis
坦白说 我发现这很有趣
and frankly found that fascinating.
好的
Okay.
或者如果您更愿意教授其他课程
Or if there's another course you'd rather teach, though.
不不不 只是我……
No, no, it's just I...
我还没看过我的论文
I haven't looked at my thesis
自从我发表了它之后 我会的
since I published it, but I will.
我可以...我可以看一看
I can... I can look through it,
我会创建一个教学大纲供你们查看
and I will create a syllabus for you to look at.
精彩的
Wonderful.
我们很高兴您能来
We're thrilled to have you.
谢谢
Thank you.
艾格尼丝 我必须告诉你一些事情
Agnes, I have to tell you something.
我恋爱了
I am in love.
—什么？—是啊！
-What? -Yeah!
而且超级超级同性恋
And like, super, super gay.
就像 比我们想象的还要快乐
Like, gayer than we thought.
噢 哇哦
Oh, wow.
天啊 和那个人在一起？
Oh, my God. With that person?
—是的 弗兰 —好的
-Yeah. Fran. -Okay.
—是的 —哇
-Yeah. -Wow.
哇 好吧 你这么开心吗？
Wow. Okay, are you so happy
-同性恋并且恋爱？-哦 我真的很喜欢
-being gay and in love? -Oh, I'm like really,
作为一名同性恋者并且恋爱 我真的很高兴
really happy being gay and in love.
噢 天哪 你一定要见见他们！
Oh, my God, you have to meet them!
是的 我完全同意 我同意
Yeah, I totally do. I do.
你...哦 Lydie
You... Oh, Lydie,
你值得被爱
you deserve to be in love
永远
all the time forever.
谢谢你 宝贝
Thank you, babe.
好吧 好吧...所以我得到了这份工作
Well, well... so I got the job.
什么？
What?
我得到了全职职位
I got the full-time position.
我的天啊！
Oh, my God!
什么？艾格尼丝！
What? Agnes!
是啊 嗯 它是 它是...
Yeah, well, it's, it's...
不如恋爱
not as good as being in love.
是的 这太神奇了
Yes it is. This is amazing.
这太棒了
This is great.
艾格尼丝
Agnes.
是啊 不 很好
Yeah, no, it's good.
艾格尼丝 你真的值得拥有这一切
You really, really earned this, Agnes.
这里是你的办公室
And here is your office.
如果你需要什么就告诉我
Let me know if you need anything,
如果灯泡熄灭了 诸如此类的事情
if a light bulb goes out, anything like that.
—谢谢 索菲 —嗯
-Thanks, Sophie. -Mm.
“这让我很震惊”
"And it struck me",
当我的自动膝盖上下移动时
as my automaton knees went up and down
我根本就不知道一件事
that I simply did not know a thing
关于我亲爱的心事
about my darling's mind
并且很有可能
and that quite possibly
在这些可怕的、幼稚的陈词滥调背后……
behind the awful, juvenile cliches...
她
there was in her
花园和黄昏
a garden and a twilight
还有宫殿的大门
and a palace gate,
昏暗而可爱的地区恰好是
dim and adorable regions which happened to be
“显然绝对禁止……”
"lucidly and absolutely forbidden..."
—沃德教授 —是的
-Professor Ward. -Yes.
抱歉 但我个人发现这本书
I'm sorry, but I personally found this book
真恶心
really disgusting.
嗯 杰里米
Well, Jeremy,
有一个世界 听到这个消息让人松了一口气
there's a world in which that's a relief to hear.
您如何看待这篇文章本身？
How did you find the writing itself?
嗯 事情是这样的 我...
Well, that's the thing is I...
我感到很生气 因为我……
I felt pissed off because I...
真的很讨厌发生的事情
really hated the stuff happening
但我真的很喜欢他说的那种东西
but I really liked the sort of stuff he was saying.
—所以我很生气 —嗯 好吧
-So I was pissed. -Mmm, okay.
有没有其他人也有同样的感觉
Was anyone else feeling that way
夹在形式之间
caught between the form,
演示本身
the presentation itself,
以及演讲的内容？
and the content of that presentation?
呃 教授……那位女士回来了
Uh, professor... that lady is back
透过小窗户看
looking through the little window thing.
她很执着
She is persistent.
就像亨伯特的愿望一样
Much like Humbert's desire
及时冻结洛丽塔
to freeze Lolita in time.
-很好 -好的 我们读吧
-Nice. -Okay. Let's read.
“因为我经常注意到 像我们这样生活
"For I often noticed that living as we did,
她和我 处在一个充满邪恶的世界里……”
she and I, in a world of total evil..."
—那么...—嗨
-So... -Hi.
莉迪订婚了
Lydie got engaged.
是的
Yeah.
婚礼什么时候举行？
When's the wedding?
现在是夏天
It's in the summer.
-你喜欢弗兰吗？-哦 是的 弗兰人很好
-Do you like Fran? -Oh, yeah. Fran is nice.
有点内敛 个子很高
Reserved, kind of. Really tall.
发生什么事了？
What's happening?
所以你得到了这份工作
So you got the job.
是的
Yes.
我想要这份工作
I wanted the job.
好的
Okay.
—你感觉不舒服吗？—是的
-Do you feel bad at all? -Yes.
但是 是因为其他原因 而不是因为这个
But, for other reasons, not because of this.
好的 嗯...
Okay, well, um...
只是因为事情对你来说很容易
just because things come easy to you
并不意味着你可以从别人那里拿走东西
doesn't mean that you get to take things from people
事情来之不易
who things don't come easy to.
对我来说事情并不容易
Things don't come easy to me.
是的 大家都喜欢你
Yes they do. Everyone likes you.
—你很聪明 你很性感 —谢谢你
-You're smart, you're hot. -Thank you.
呃 不是那样的
Ew, not like that.
洛根喜欢你 德文也喜欢你
Logan likes you, Devin likes you.
Lydie 喜欢你
Lydie likes you.
德克尔喜欢你
Decker likes you.
嗯 你不喜欢我
Well, you don't like me.
这是真的
That's true.
你知道 当我想到这一点时
You know, when I think about it,
我认为德克尔实际上恨我
I think Decker actually hated me.
你是他选中的人
You were his chosen one.
这真是太疯狂了
That's a completely insane thing to say.
不
No.
因为当你喜欢某人或者
Because when you like someone or, like,
当你尊重某人时
when you respect someone,
人们对待你的方式有些不同
there are some ways people treat you
这是一种方法
that are one way.
尊重 并且喜欢
Respectful, and like,
你是一个活着、呼吸着的人
you're a person who lives and breathes
并独立思考
and thinks for them self.
但有些人对待你的方式却不是那样的
And then some ways people treat you are not that way,
而且它们很糟糕
and they're bad.
好吧 嗯 我和他上床了……
All right. Well, um, I fucked him...
他甚至没有花时间
and, uh, he didn't even take the time
亲自给我论文做笔记 所以……
to give me in-person notes on my thesis. So...
你跟他上床了？
You fucked him?
是的
Yeah.
你想要那个吗？
Did you want that?
想要啥？
Want what?
是故意的吗？
Was it on purpose?
是的 这是故意的
Yes, it was on purpose.
我们进行了大约五分钟的性爱
We had, like, five minute sex.
还行吧 我吃过更好的了
It was just okay. I've had better.
我们关门了 这里不能停车
We're closed. You can't park here.
哦 糟糕 哦 糟糕
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
听着 我很抱歉对你大喊大叫
Look, I'm sorry I yelled at you.
我的孩子汉克也会出现呼吸困难的情况
My kid, Hank, gets these breathing attacks too,
有时真的很糟糕
real bad sometimes.
我知道你很害怕
I know you're scared,
但你已经离开了道路 坐在车里
but you're off the road, you're in your car,
你没事
and you're okay.
我要呼吸 你也和我一起呼吸
I'm gonna breathe and you breathe with me.
好吗？你跟着就行
Okay? You just follow.
好吗？准备好了吗？在……
All right? You ready? In...
出局……二、三、四、五
Out... two, three, four, five.
在...
In...
出局……二、三、四、五
Out... two, three, four, five.
在...
In...
出局……二、三、四、五
Out... two, three, four, five.
在...二、三
In... two, three.
出去...
Out...
二、三、四、五
Two, three, four, five.
我必须说实话
I gotta be honest,
我不太会这样呼吸
I don't really breathe like that,
但感觉很好
but it feels good.
你还好吗？
You doing okay?
对你有好处
Good for you.
你想要一个三明治吗？
You want a sandwich?
我想在这里摆放桌子
I wanted to put tables out here
所以 你知道 人们不会坐在地上
so, people, you know, wouldn't sit on the ground.
这是一个美味的三明治
It's a good sandwich.
你不应该吃一个好三明治
You shouldn't eat a good sandwich
当你坐在地上时
while you're sitting on the ground
鸽子拉屎的地方
where the pigeons shit.
任何
Whatever.
但他们说 你们共享一个……
But they said, you share a...
垃圾场里有停车场
a parking lot with the guys at the dump.
所以你得问问垃圾场的人
So you gotta ask the guys at the dump.
我才不会问垃圾场里的人呢！
No fucking way I'm asking the guys at the dump!
他妈的混蛋
Fucking assholes.
这很好
This is good.
是的 当然好
Yeah, of course it's good.
你没有三明治店
You don't have a sandwich shop,
你做的三明治不太好
you don't make a good sandwich.
辛辣的
Spicy.
卡拉布里亚辣椒 非常昂贵
Calabrian chili, very expensive.
艾格尼丝
Agnes.
咦？
Huh?
—艾格尼丝？—是的
-Agnes? -Yeah.
-呃 -哇哦
-Ugh. -Whoa,
你们听起来就像垃圾堆里来的坏人
you sound like the mean guys from the dump.
嘿！我……我对此感到不满
Hey! I res... I resent that.
那些家伙都是混蛋 说实话 我不是混蛋
Those guys are assholes. I'm honest, not an asshole.
你有个儿子？
You have a son?
他是个混蛋
He's an asshole.
汉克
Hank.
—汉克是……—呃……
-Hank is... -Ugh...
你不必告诉我
You don't have to tell me.
听起来太像“honk”这个词了
Sounds too much like the word honk.
—你有孩子吗？—没有
-You have kids? -No.
想要一些吗？
Want some?
呃……好吧 我真的无法想象自己变老
Uh... Well, I can't really imagine myself old.
你以为我想象中的自己是这样的吗？
You think I imagined myself like this?
不 不管你信不信
No, believe it or not,
我没有想到我会
I did not think I would end up
看上去就像一个有嘴的山药
looking like a yam with a mouth on it.
但我们就在这儿
But here we are.
这也会发生在你身上
It'll happen to you.
你不会知道是什么击中了你
You won't know what hit you.
我遇到了一件非常糟糕的事情
Something pretty bad happened to me,
这可能就是我行为怪异的原因
so that's probably why I'm acting weird.
有多糟糕？
How bad?
一...
Um...
我想真的很糟糕
I guess really bad.
你不知道这很糟糕吗？
You don't know it's bad?
不 我知道这很糟糕
No, I know it's bad.
但主要是因为每当我告诉别人这件事时
But mainly because whenever I tell anyone about it,
他们看起来真的为我感到害怕
they look really scared for me.
除了我的朋友 但她搬走了
Except for my friend, but she moved away.
有时候我一想到这件事就觉得难过
And then sometimes I feel bad when I think about it,
因为...
because...
我记得那些时刻
I remember moments of it,
我可以感觉到我的身体
and I can feel in my body
那真的很糟糕
that it was really bad.
但有时我不会去想它
But then sometimes I don't think about it,
这很奇怪
which is weird.
当我不去想这件事时 我就会感到内疚
And I feel guilty when I don't think about it.
刚刚发生的事吗？
Did it just happen?
这就是你气喘吁吁的原因吗？
Is that why you were huffing and puffing?
不 是三...
No, it was three...
三年前
a little over three years ago.
嗯 时间并不多
Well, that's not that much time.
我的意思是 这需要很多时间
I mean, it's a lot of time,
但时间也不多了
but it's not that much time, too.
是的
Yeah.
你是...
Are you...
你家还好吗？
okay in your house?
我有一只猫
I have a cat.
好的
Okay.
奥尔加 这到底是怎么回事？
Olga, what the fuck?
奥尔加 去睡觉吧
Olga, go to bed.
呃 奥尔加 你在我的床上拉屎了吗？
Ugh, Olga, did you shit in my bed?
哦！奥尔加 这到底是怎么回事？
Oh! Olga, what the fuck?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
哦 如果你想杀死它
Oh, if you wanted to kill it,
你应该直接杀了它！
you should have just killed it!
好的 我回来了 我回来了
Okay. I'm coming back. I'm coming back.
很快就结束了 好的 好的
It'll be over soon. Okay. Okay.
好的 我需要什么？我在寻找什么？
Okay. What do I need? What am I looking for?
哦！一个包 一个包！我有一个包！
Oh! A bag, a bag! I got a bag!
我要回来了！
I'm coming back!
我回来了 我回来了 真的很抱歉
I'm back, I'm back, I'm so sorry.
你还好嗎？
Are you okay?
不 不 你不会死的 你正在死去
No, no you're not, you're dying.
进袋子里
Get in the bag.
放进袋子里就可以了
Just go in the bag.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
哦 天哪
Oh, God.
加文！
Gavin!
艾格尼丝 你还好吗？
Agnes, are you okay?
艾格尼丝？什么……
Agnes? What...
你还好嗎？
Are you okay?
你会来操我嗎？
Will you come fuck me?
是的
Yes.
等一下 等一下 我需要鞋子
Wait, wait. I need shoes.
我嗯……我确实需要鞋子
I um... I do need shoes.
一秒钟
One second.
哦 嘿
Oh, hey.
我可以小便吗？
Can I pee?
哦 是的 当然
Oh, yeah. Definitely.
我可以进去吗？
Can I get in?
哦 在洗澡吗？
Oh, in the bath?
是的
Yeah.
呃 当然
Uh, sure.
我只是要在这里转一圈
I'm just gonna turn around here.
别介意我
Don't mind me.
你不必隐藏它
You don't have to hide it.
现在还很小
It's small right now.
男人真是奇怪
Men are so weird.
谢谢
Thank you.
噢 那太好了
Oh, that's nice.
温度适宜
It's a good temperature.
谢谢
Thank you.
我对自己隐藏自己的阴茎感到很尴尬
I'm embarrassed that I was hiding my dick.
没关系
That's okay.
我把头发放在胸部上
I put my hair over my boobs.
如此真实
So true.
抱歉 浴缸太小了
I'm sorry the bathtub is so small.
这个浴缸？
This bathtub?
不 很好
No, it's good.
如果我坐在你后面呢？
What if I sat behind you?
—为什么？—那么 呃……
-Why? -So, uh...
它可能就像一个拥抱
it could be like a hug.
好的
Okay.
-是啊是啊
-Yeah? -Yeah.
哦 等等 我可以看看吗？
Oh, wait. Can I look at it?
嗎？
At my dick?
是的
Yeah.
唔...
Hmm...
我从未见过如此柔软的
I've never seen one that soft.
好吧 我觉得那只是让我做了恶梦
Okay, I think that just gave me nightmares
未来十年
for the next decade.
不 我的意思是 你永远不可能看到他们那样
No, I mean, you just never get to see them like that.
他们这样会更好
They're better like this.
唔...
Hmm...
好的 我说完了
Okay, I'm done.
毫米
Mm.
你以为你想要每个人都有的东西吗？
Do you think you want the stuff that everyone has?
你是什么意思？
What do you mean?
就像 呃
Like, uh,
家庭或者其他什么的 我不知道
family or whatever. I don't know.
你想要那些东西吗？
Do you want that stuff?
与你？
With you?
不
No.
不 我的意思是 这是你的问题
No, I mean, it was your question.
是的 我想要那个东西
Yeah. I want that stuff.
好的
Nice.
你？
Do you?
出色地...
Well...
你知道 可能只是为了让 Lydie 更亲近一些……
You know, probably just to keep Lydie closer...
但我没有看到
but I don't see it.
在哪里看到？
See it where?
就像在我的脑海里一样
Like, in my head.
我不认为自己会变老或者有孩子
I don't see myself getting older or having kids.
我看不到我自己
I don't see myself.
我认为你会是一位伟大的妈妈
I think you'd be a great mom.
为什么？
Why?
您非常友善
You're very nice.
我没那么好
I'm not that nice.
人们总是说他们不想要孩子
People always say they don't want a kid,
但后来情况发生了变化
but then things change.
我们想要什么等等...
What we want and stuff...
我认为它会改变
I think it changes.
太冷了
It's too cold.
我认为这很好
I think it's nice.
嗨！耶！
Hi! Yay!
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
—我想你 —我想你
-I missed you. -I missed you.
我太想你了 天哪
I missed you so much. Oh, my God.
宝宝在这儿吗？
Is the baby here?
宝宝来了 宝宝来了
The baby's here. The baby's here.
—嗨 艾格尼丝 —嗨 弗兰
-Hi, Agnes. -Hi, Fran.
弗兰
Fran.
— 什么事？— 记得吗？
-Yes? -Remember?
噢 噢！
Oh, Oh!
是的
Yeah.
大日子！
Big day!
确实
Definitely.
好吧 亲爱的……
All right, sweetie...
那么 你很高兴你来了？
So, you're glad you came?
我实在是太太太太高兴了
I'm so, so, so, so glad.
现在我知道了阴道爆炸
And now I know what an exploding vagina
看起来像
looks like.
嗯
Mhmm.
—所以要诚实 —嗯
-So be honest. -Mhmm.
你喜欢她吗？
Do you like her?
—我的宝贝？—是的
-My baby? -Yeah.
是的
Yeah.
—我真的很喜欢我的孩子 —嗯 那真的很好
-I really like my baby. -Well, that's really good.
你还喜欢我 对吗？
And you still like me, right?
是的 艾格尼丝
Yes, Agnes.
—我爱你们俩 —太棒了
-I love you both. -Cool.
—莉迪？—嗯？
-Lydie? -Yeah?
-宝贝 你会抱住宝宝吗？-好的 当然 等一下
-Babe, will you grab the baby? -Yeah, of course. One second.
-嘿 -嗨
-Hey. -Hi.
—你需要帮忙吗？—不 不 不
-You need help with the stuff? -No, no, no.
—好的 —嗨
-Okay. -Hi.
么么哒
Muah.
—呵呵
-Hi. -Hi.
看看这个
Look at this.
哦 让我拿一个
Oh, let me grab one.
不 我喜欢抱着它们
No, I love holding them.
那么 你是...哦 是的
So, are you... oh, yes.
嗨 哇哦
Hi. Wow.
她的面容更加丰满
She has much more of a face.
嗯
Mhmm.
小怪异婴儿珍妮
Little freaky baby Janie.
哦 不是珍妮 只是在扮演简
Oh, not Janie. Just doing Jane.
你好 很高兴再次见到你
Hi, nice to see you again.
哦 哦
Oh, oh.
噢 没关系
Oh, it's okay.
—哦 我没有...—没关系
-Oh, I didn't... -It's okay.
这种事经常发生
It happens all the time.
噢 真的吗 会发生这种事吗？
Oh, really, does that happen?
这是我的脸吗？
Is it my face?
你好 是我的脸吗？
Hello, is it my face?
灯塔日！
Lighthouse day!
灯塔日
Lighthouse day.
弗兰 弗兰
Fran. Fran.
灯塔日！
Lighthouse day!
灯塔日
Lighthouse day.
珍妮 珍妮 灯塔日！
Janie, Janie. Lighthouse day!
她其实没睡觉
She actually didn't sleep
—非常好 所以 —哦
-super well, so. -Oh.
是的 我们真的非常非常累
Yeah, we're really, really fucking tired.
是的 我不认为她会参加
Yeah, I don't think she's gonna be in for,
就像今天发生的一件大事
like, a big thing today.
婴儿？
The baby?
好吧 她只是个婴儿 她可以做任何事
Well, she's just a baby, she could do whatever.
我的意思是 并非如此
I mean, not really.
你们两个去吧 我会留在这里
But you two go. I will stay here.
哦 真的吗？好的
Oh, really? Okay.
我真的很想让你看看它
I really wanted you to see it.
宝贝 我以后一定会看到的 没关系
Babe, I will see it at some point. It's okay.
好的
Okay.
不
No.
不 你们两个去吧
No, you two go.
不 不 必须有人陪着简
No, no, someone has to stay with Jane.
我会做的
I'll do it.
真的吗？
Really?
哦 简其实很讲究
Oh, Jane is actually really particular.
我会做
I will do it.
哦 我的天哪 艾格尼丝 非常感谢你
Oh, my God. Agnes, thank you so much.
弗兰 我们自由了！我们自由了
Fran, we're free! We're free.
灯塔非常浪漫
The lighthouse is very romantic.
你们两个应该单独在一起
You two should be there alone together.
再生一个孩子或者其他什么的
Make another baby or whatever.
大概二十分钟 就是这样
Like, twenty minutes, that's it.
有一个问题 如果她杀了我怎么办？
One question. What if she kills me?
她不会杀了你的
She's not gonna kill you.
嘿...
Hey...
别把她摔了
Don't drop her.
不 我不会抛弃她
No. I won't drop her.
好的...
Okay...
好的
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
干得好
Here you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
—给你 宝贝 —谢谢你
-Here you go, babe. -Thank you.
莉迪亚？
Lydie?
是的？
Yeah?
我该对她说什么呢？
What do I say to her?
宝贝 你什么也不用说
Babe, you don't have to say anything.
二十分钟
Twenty minutes.
你好
Hi.
我是艾格尼丝
I'm Agnes.
很奇怪有一天你会成为一个人
Pretty weird you're gonna be a person someday.
无意冒犯 但你现在看上去很疯狂
No offense, but you look insane right now.
皮肤和少量毛发
Skin and just a small amount of hair.
不用担心
Don't worry.
不久之后就不会这样了
It won't be like that in a little.
这样可以吗或者...
Is this okay or...
好的
All right.
我就把你放下来
I'll put you down.
哦 我去接你
Oh. I'll pick you back up.
好的 好的 好的
Okay, okay, okay.
你看上去真甜美
You're so sweet looking.
等你长大了 什么都可以告诉我
When you grow up, you can tell me whatever.
比如 如果你有一个想法
Like, if you have a thought
你会觉得这个想法很糟糕
and you're like, that's a bad thought,
我可能也有同样的想法 但是
I probably had that same thought but, like,
糟糕十倍
ten times worse.
所以你直接告诉我就可以了
So you can just tell me.
我永远不会被这个吓到
I'll never be scared by that.
如果有人对你做了坏事……
If someone does something bad to you...
如果有人说了一些可怕的事情......
If someone says something scary...
如果你想自杀
If you wanna kill yourself
用铅笔或者小刀或者其他什么东西
with like a pencil or a knife or whatever,
你可以直接告诉我
you can just tell me.
我永远不会告诉你你让我害怕
I'll never tell you you're scaring me.
我只能说 是的
I'll just say, yeah.
我知道
I know.
有时候就是这样
It's just like that sometimes.
是的
Yeah.
对不起
I'm sorry
不好的事情将会发生在你身上
that bad things are gonna happen to you.
我希望他们不会
I hope they don't.
如果我能阻止某件事变坏
If I can ever stop something from being bad,
让我知道
let me know.
但有时糟糕的事情就会发生
But sometimes bad stuff just happens.
这就是为什么我为你感到难过
That's why I feel bad for you,
在某种程度上
in a way.
你还活着 但你还不知道这一点
That you're alive and you don't know that yet.
但我仍然可以听
But I can still listen
不要害怕
and not be scared.
这很好
So that's good.
或者至少是这样的
Or that's something, at least.